[
    {
        "categoria": "Matematicas",
        "pregunta": "2x+34b+42xy",
        "respuesta": "2x(1+21y)+34b",
        "incorrecta1": "2x(2+42b)+34y",
        "incorrecta2": "2x(1+42xy)+34b",
        "incorrecta3": "x(2x+34b+42y)",
		"objectFit":"cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"x²+5x+6",
        "respuesta":"x(x + 5) + 6",
        "incorrecta1":"(x+5)(x+6)",
        "incorrecta2":"x2(1+5x) + 6",
        "incorrecta3":"x(x+5y) + 6",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
    },
    {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"ax+ea+ea³+eb",
        "respuesta":"a(x+e+ea²) + eb)",
        "incorrecta1":"ax(1+e+ea)+eb",
        "incorrecta2":"ax(1+e+ea)+eb",
        "incorrecta3":"a(x+e+ea²) - eb",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
       },
       {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"2xb + 54b + 10b",
        "respuesta":"2b(x+27+5)",
        "incorrecta1":"b(x+54b+10)",
        "incorrecta2":"x(b+54x+10)",
        "incorrecta3":"2x(b+27+5)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
       },
       {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"5x³-15x²",
        "respuesta":"5x²(x-3)",
        "incorrecta1":"2x²(7x-17)",
        "incorrecta2":"2x(7x²-17x)",
        "incorrecta3":"5x(x²-3)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"10y",
        "respuesta":"2(20y-15y)",            
        "incorrecta1":"y(20y-10y)",
        "incorrecta2":"5(5y)",
        "incorrecta3":"2y(2+2)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"x²⁵ + x¹⁵y",
        "respuesta":"x(x¹⁵+x⁵y)",
        "incorrecta1":"x²⁰(x⁵+xy",
        "incorrecta2":"x¹⁵(x10+x5)",
        "incorrecta3":"x¹⁵(x¹⁰+x)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"50x²+20x+8",
        "respuesta":"2(5x+2)²",
        "incorrecta1":"25x(2x+20)",
        "incorrecta2":"25x(2x+20)+8",
        "incorrecta3":"2(5x+2)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"xy(9999x+x)",
        "respuesta":"10000x2y",
        "incorrecta1":"9999xy + x",
        "incorrecta2":"25x(2x+20)+8",
        "incorrecta3":"2(5x+2)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"a3b-ab²+a²b-ab3",
        "respuesta":"ab(a²-b+a-b²)",
        "incorrecta1":"a(a²b-ab²+ab-ab³)",
        "incorrecta2":"b(a³-ab+a²b-ab²)",
        "incorrecta3":"a²b²(a-b+a-b)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
       "pregunta":" 45xby + 185xy + 25by + 50y",
        "respuesta":"5y(9xb + 37x + 5b + 10)",
        "incorrecta1":"5y(9xb + 37 + 5b + 10)",
        "incorrecta2":"2y(18xb + 85x + 12b + 25)",
        "incorrecta3":"45x(by + 185xy + 25by + 50y)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"5x-5xy",
        "respuesta":"5x(1-y)",
        "incorrecta1":"5x(x-y)",
        "incorrecta2":"25(x-xy)",
        "incorrecta3":"10(x+y)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        },
        {
        "categoria":"Matematicas",
        "pregunta":"25x-45",
        "respuesta":"5(5x-9)",
        "incorrecta1":"5x(x-9)",
        "incorrecta2":"5x-9)(5x+9)",
        "incorrecta3":"x(25-45)",
        "ObjectFit":"cover"
        }
]
